[
 {
   "NR": 1,
   "Question": " In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?",
   "Answer": " Knee"
 },
 {
   "NR": 2,
   "Question": " What is the name of the main antagonist in the Shakespeare play Othello?",
   "Answer": " Iago"
 },
 {
   "NR": 3,
   "Question": " What element is denoted by the chemical symbol Sn in the periodic table?",
   "Answer": " Tin"
 },
 {
   "NR": 4,
   "Question": " What is the name of the 1976 film about the Watergate scandal, starring Robert Redford and Dustin Hoffman?",
   "Answer": " All the President’s Men"
 },
 {
   "NR": 5,
   "Question": " How many of Henry VIII’s wives were called Catherine?",
   "Answer": "3"
 },
 {
   "NR": 6,
   "Question": " What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2019?",
   "Answer": " Olivia"
 },
 {
   "NR": 7,
   "Question": " Which comedian was the second permanent host of Never Mind the Buzzcocks after Mark Lamarr?",
   "Answer": " Simon Amstell"
 },
 {
   "NR": 8,
   "Question": " Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?",
   "Answer": " Call of Duty"
 },
 {
   "NR": 9,
   "Question": " In what US State is the city Nashville?",
   "Answer": " Tennessee"
 },
 {
   "NR": 10,
   "Question": " Which rock band was founded by Trent Reznor in 1988?",
   "Answer": " Nine Inch Nails"
 },
 {
   "NR": 11,
   "Question": " What is the currency of Denmark?",
   "Answer": " Krone"
 },
 {
   "NR": 12,
   "Question": " Which Tennis Grand Slam is played on a clay surface?",
   "Answer": " The French Open (Roland Garros)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 13,
   "Question": " In which European country would you find the Rijksmuseum?",
   "Answer": " Netherlands"
 },
 {
   "NR": 14,
   "Question": " How many films have Al Pacino and Robert De Niro appeared in together?",
   "Answer": " Four (The Godfather Part 2, Heat, Righteous Kill, The Irishman)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 15,
   "Question": " What was the old name for a Snickers bar before it changed in 1990?",
   "Answer": " Marathon"
 },
 {
   "NR": 16,
   "Question": " Who was the head of state in Japan during the second world war?",
   "Answer": " Emperor Hirohito"
 },
 {
   "NR": 17,
   "Question": " What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
   "Answer": " Mercury"
 },
 {
   "NR": 18,
   "Question": " Who wrote the novels Gone Girl and Sharp Objects?",
   "Answer": " Gillian Flynn"
 },
 {
   "NR": 19,
   "Question": " Which legendary surrealist artist is famous for painting melting clocks?",
   "Answer": " Salvador Dali"
 },
 {
   "NR": 20,
   "Question": " Which football club plays its home games at Loftus Road",
   "Answer": " Queen’s Park Rangers"
 },
 {
   "NR": 21,
   "Question": " Continental United States has 4 time zones, can you name them?",
   "Answer": " Pacific, Mountain, Central, Eastern"
 },
 {
   "NR": 22,
   "Question": " What was the Turkish city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
   "Answer": " Constantinople"
 },
 {
   "NR": 23,
   "Question": " From which US city do the band The Killers originate?",
   "Answer": " Las Vegas"
 },
 {
   "NR": 24,
   "Question": " Name the Coffee shop in US sitcom Friends",
   "Answer": " Central Perk"
 },
 {
   "NR": 25,
   "Question": " How many human players are there on each side in a polo match?",
   "Answer": " Four"
 },
 {
   "NR": 26,
   "Question": " In what year did Tony Blair become British Prime Minister?",
   "Answer": "1997"
 },
 {
   "NR": 27,
   "Question": " How many times has England won the men’s football World Cup?",
   "Answer": " Once (1966)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 28,
   "Question": " What is the capital of New Zealand?",
   "Answer": " Wellington"
 },
 {
   "NR": 29,
   "Question": " Street artist Banksy is originally associated with which British city?",
   "Answer": " Bristol"
 },
 {
   "NR": 30,
   "Question": " From what grain is the Japanese spirit Sake made?",
   "Answer": " Rice"
 },
 {
   "NR": 31,
   "Question": " How many permanent teeth does a dog have?",
   "Answer": "42"
 },
 {
   "NR": 32,
   "Question": " What is the most sold flavour of Walker’s crisps?",
   "Answer": " Cheese and Onion"
 },
 {
   "NR": 33,
   "Question": " What is the full postcode of the Houses of Parliament?",
   "Answer": " SW1A 0AA"
 },
 {
   "NR": 34,
   "Question": " What is someone who believes in antidisestablishmentarianism opposed to the disestablishment of?",
   "Answer": " The Church of England"
 },
 {
   "NR": 35,
   "Question": " What does the Latin Tempus mean in English?",
   "Answer": " Time"
 },
 {
   "NR": 36,
   "Question": " How many chukkers are there in a polo match?",
   "Answer": "6"
 },
 {
   "NR": 37,
   "Question": " On average how far away is the moon from the earth in miles?",
   "Answer": "238,000"
 },
 {
   "NR": 38,
   "Question": " What’s longer, a nautical mile or a mile?",
   "Answer": " Nautical mile (it’s 1.15 Miles)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 39,
   "Question": " Saying the name of what dried fruit used to be used to encourage people to smile before a photo in the 1800s, before the phrase “cheese?”",
   "Answer": " Prunes"
 },
 {
   "NR": 40,
   "Question": " Which country in the world is believed to have the most miles of motorway?",
   "Answer": " China"
 },
 {
   "NR": 41,
   "Question": " What is the name of Dua Lipa’s 2020 album release?",
   "Answer": " Future Nostalgia"
 },
 {
   "NR": 42,
   "Question": " Name the song and the artist for the following lyric: “Maybe I’m foolish, maybe I’m blind, thinking I can see through this and see what’s behind”",
   "Answer": " Human by Rag’n’Bone Man"
 },
 {
   "NR": 43,
   "Question": " Matt Goss, Luke Goss and Craig Logan made up which band?",
   "Answer": " Bros"
 },
 {
   "NR": 44,
   "Question": " In what year did The Beatles split up?",
   "Answer": "1970"
 },
 {
   "NR": 45,
   "Question": " What is rapper P Diddy’s real name?",
   "Answer": " Sean Combs"
 },
 {
   "NR": 46,
   "Question": " Complete this Spice Girls lyric: “If you wanna be my [BLANK], you gotta get with my friends”",
   "Answer": " Lover (from the song Wannabe)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 47,
   "Question": " Which two musicians collaborated on Another Way To Die, the theme song to 2008’s 007: Quantum of Solace?",
   "Answer": " Alicia Keys and Jack White"
 },
 {
   "NR": 48,
   "Question": " Gary and Martin Kemp were in what band?",
   "Answer": " Spandau Ballet"
 },
 {
   "NR": 49,
   "Question": " In what decade was pop icon Madonna born?",
   "Answer": " 1950s (1958)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 50,
   "Question": " Which two country singers famously sang together on 1983 song Islands in the Stream?",
   "Answer": " Kenny Rogers and Dolly Parton"
 },
 {
   "NR": 51,
   "Question": " Who won 2019’s Sports Personality of the Year?",
   "Answer": " Ben Stokes"
 },
 {
   "NR": 52,
   "Question": " How many goals did England score (excluding penalty shoot-outs) at the Mens’ 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
   "Answer": "12"
 },
 {
   "NR": 53,
   "Question": " Ben Stokes inspired England’s 2019 Cricket World Cup final victory over New Zealand – who scored the second-highest number of runs in the match for England?",
   "Answer": " Jos Buttler"
 },
 {
   "NR": 54,
   "Question": " How many different teams have won the Premier League since the start of the inaugural season in 1992/93?",
   "Answer": " Six (Man Utd, Man City, Chelsea, Arsenal, Leicester, Blackburn)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 55,
   "Question": " What are the five colours of the Olympic rings?",
   "Answer": " Blue, Yellow, Black, Green and Red"
 },
 {
   "NR": 56,
   "Question": " What score did cricketing legend Don Bradman average as a batsman across his career?",
   "Answer": "99.94"
 },
 {
   "NR": 57,
   "Question": " At which venue is the British Grand Prix held?",
   "Answer": " Silverstone"
 },
 {
   "NR": 58,
   "Question": " How many horses are on each team in a polo match?",
   "Answer": " Four"
 },
 {
   "NR": 59,
   "Question": " Where is the US Masters golf tournament held?",
   "Answer": " Augusta National Golf Club"
 },
 {
   "NR": 60,
   "Question": " Which European city hosted the 1936 Summer Olympics?",
   "Answer": " Berlin"
 },
 {
   "NR": 61,
   "Question": " When did Big Brother first air on Channel 4?",
   "Answer": "2000"
 },
 {
   "NR": 62,
   "Question": " Who was the first presenter of the X Factor in the UK?",
   "Answer": " Kate Thornton"
 },
 {
   "NR": 63,
   "Question": " Which actor played the ninth reincarnation of the Doctor in Doctor Who?",
   "Answer": " Christopher Eccleston"
 },
 {
   "NR": 64,
   "Question": " The Simpsons was the spin-off show of which American sketch series?",
   "Answer": " The Tracey Ullman Show"
 },
 {
   "NR": 65,
   "Question": " What was the name of the tower block where Del Boy and Rodney Trotter lived in Only Fools and Horses?",
   "Answer": " Nelson Mandela House"
 },
 {
   "NR": 66,
   "Question": " Gillian Anderson plays a therapist in which hit Netflix show?",
   "Answer": " Sex Education"
 },
 {
   "NR": 67,
   "Question": " What is the name of the fictional borough of Melbourne where Australian soap Neighbours is set?",
   "Answer": " Erinsborough"
 },
 {
   "NR": 68,
   "Question": " EastEnders began broadcasting on BBC One in which year?",
   "Answer": "1985"
 },
 {
   "NR": 69,
   "Question": " Who is the longest serving presenter of the BBC children’s show Blue Peter?",
   "Answer": " John Noakes (12 years from 1965-1978)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 70,
   "Question": " What is the name of Mackenzie Crook’s character in sitcom The Office?",
   "Answer": " Gareth Keenan"
 },
 {
   "NR": 71,
   "Question": " Which British actor will play Batman in the upcoming reboot directed by Matt Reeves?",
   "Answer": " Robert Pattinson"
 },
 {
   "NR": 72,
   "Question": " What is the name of The Bride, played by Uma Thurman, in Quentin Tarantino’s Kill Bill franchise? ",
   "Answer": " Beatrix Kiddo"
 },
 {
   "NR": 73,
   "Question": " Which colour pill does Neo swallow in The Matrix?",
   "Answer": " Red"
 },
 {
   "NR": 74,
   "Question": " Name the composer behind the soundtracks of The Lion King, Inception and Pirates of the Caribbean",
   "Answer": " Hanz Zimmer"
 },
 {
   "NR": 75,
   "Question": " Which 2014 Seth Rogan film caused the North Korean government to threaten action against the United States?",
   "Answer": " The Interview"
 },
 {
   "NR": 76,
   "Question": " Name the first actor to play Dumbledore in the Harry Potter films",
   "Answer": " Richard Harris"
 },
 {
   "NR": 77,
   "Question": " Which Catastrophe star makes a cameo in Deadpool 2 as Peter?",
   "Answer": " Rob Delaney"
 },
 {
   "NR": 78,
   "Question": " Which husband-wife duo starred in 2018’s horror film A Quiet Place?",
   "Answer": " Emily Blunt and John Krasinski"
 },
 {
   "NR": 79,
   "Question": " Which 2019 film won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Film this year? ",
   "Answer": " Cats"
 },
 {
   "NR": 80,
   "Question": " What does Bridget Jones name her baby in the film series’s third instalment?",
   "Answer": " William"
 },
 {
   "NR": 81,
   "Question": " How many spice options are there at Nandos?",
   "Answer": " 6 – Plain…(ish), Passion Fruit and Mango, Lemon and Herb, Medium, Hot, Extra Hot"
 },
 {
   "NR": 82,
   "Question": " Which soft drink is commonly associated with Scotland?",
   "Answer": " Irn-Bru"
 },
 {
   "NR": 83,
   "Question": " According to McDonalds’ official website, how many calories does a regular Big Mac contain? (Accept to the nearest 10)",
   "Answer": "508"
 },
 {
   "NR": 84,
   "Question": " What are the two main ingredients of a Dark and Stormy cocktail?",
   "Answer": " Dark rum, Ginger Beer"
 },
 {
   "NR": 85,
   "Question": " Name the 2019 winner of the Great British Bake Off",
   "Answer": " David (Atherton)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 86,
   "Question": " Gouda is a popular cheese originating from which country?",
   "Answer": " The Netherlands"
 },
 {
   "NR": 87,
   "Question": " A screwdriver cocktail is orange juice, ice and which spirit?",
   "Answer": " Vodka"
 },
 {
   "NR": 88,
   "Question": " Which southern Italian city is usually credited as the birthplace of the pizza?",
   "Answer": " Naples"
 },
 {
   "NR": 89,
   "Question": " What number is found in reference to their varieties on Heinz products?",
   "Answer": "57"
 },
 {
   "NR": 90,
   "Question": " Pret a Manger is a popular sandwich chain in the UK, but what does the French name mean in English?",
   "Answer": " Ready to eat"
 },
 {
   "NR": 91,
   "Question": " What is the capital city of Australia?",
   "Answer": " Canberra"
 },
 {
   "NR": 92,
   "Question": " Which US state was Donald Trump born in?",
   "Answer": " New York"
 },
 {
   "NR": 93,
   "Question": " If you completed the Three Peaks challenge, which three UK mountains would you have climbed?",
   "Answer": " Ben Nevis, Snowdon, Scafell Pike"
 },
 {
   "NR": 94,
   "Question": " Which UK city is situated further west – Bristol or Edinburgh?",
   "Answer": " Edinburgh"
 },
 {
   "NR": 95,
   "Question": " How many countries are there in the region of Europe? (Recognised by the United Nations)",
   "Answer": "44"
 },
 {
   "NR": 96,
   "Question": " What is the capital of Finland?",
   "Answer": " Helsinki"
 },
 {
   "NR": 97,
   "Question": " What is the currency of Vietnam?",
   "Answer": " Vietnamese dong"
 },
 {
   "NR": 98,
   "Question": " What language is spoken in Brazil?",
   "Answer": " Portuguese"
 },
 {
   "NR": 99,
   "Question": " What do the French call the English Channel?",
   "Answer": " la Manche"
 },
 {
   "NR": 100,
   "Question": " How many permanent members are there on the UN security council?",
   "Answer": " Five: China, France, Russian Federation, United Kingdom, United States"
 },
 {
   "NR": 101,
   "Question": " How many notes are there in a musical scale?",
   "Answer": "7"
 },
 {
   "NR": 102,
   "Question": " What temperature centigrade does water boil at?",
   "Answer": " 100 degrees centigrade"
 },
 {
   "NR": 103,
   "Question": " What company is also the name of one of the longest rivers in the world?",
   "Answer": " Amazon"
 },
 {
   "NR": 104,
   "Question": " What in the animal kingdom is a doe?",
   "Answer": " A female deer"
 },
 {
   "NR": 105,
   "Question": " What is the tallest mountain in the world?",
   "Answer": " Mount Everest"
 },
 {
   "NR": 106,
   "Question": " How many centimetres in a metre",
   "Answer": "100"
 },
 {
   "NR": 107,
   "Question": " What language is spoken in Norway?",
   "Answer": " Norwegian"
 },
 {
   "NR": 108,
   "Question": " What is the busiest airport in Britain called?",
   "Answer": " London Heathrow"
 },
 {
   "NR": 109,
   "Question": " Who is next in line to the British throne after Queen Elizabeth II",
   "Answer": " Prince Charles"
 },
 {
   "NR": 110,
   "Question": " What number is a baker’s dozen?",
   "Answer": "13"
 },
 {
   "NR": 111,
   "Question": " Who played Gunther in Friends?",
   "Answer": " James Michael Tyler"
 },
 {
   "NR": 112,
   "Question": " In which year did the original UK version of The Office air?",
   "Answer": "2001"
 },
 {
   "NR": 113,
   "Question": " What was legendary comedy actor Oliver Hardy’s real first name at birth?",
   "Answer": " Norvell"
 },
 {
   "NR": 114,
   "Question": " What is Sheldon Cooper’s one-word catchphrase in The Big Bang Theory?",
   "Answer": " Bazinga"
 },
 {
   "NR": 115,
   "Question": " Name the five ingredients demanded by one of Basil Fawlty’s guests to make the infamous Waldorf Salad",
   "Answer": " Celery, apple, walnuts, grapes, mayonnaise"
 },
 {
   "NR": 116,
   "Question": " Complete the name of the classic British sitcom: Steptoe and [blank]",
   "Answer": " Son"
 },
 {
   "NR": 117,
   "Question": " Who played the Prime Minister, Jim Hacker, in Yes, Prime Minister?",
   "Answer": " Paul Eddington"
 },
 {
   "NR": 118,
   "Question": " What was the name of Ronnie Barker’s character in Open All Hours?",
   "Answer": " Albert Arkwright, usually known just as Arkwright"
 },
 {
   "NR": 119,
   "Question": " Who plays comedy character Alan Partridge?",
   "Answer": " Steve Coogan"
 },
 {
   "NR": 120,
   "Question": " Name the characters played by David Mitchell and Robert Webb in Peep Show",
   "Answer": " Mark Corrigan and Jeremy Usborne"
 },
 {
   "NR": 121,
   "Question": " Who is the Special in the Lego Movie?",
   "Answer": " Emmet Brickowski"
 },
 {
   "NR": 122,
   "Question": " What colour are most buses in London?",
   "Answer": " Red"
 },
 {
   "NR": 123,
   "Question": " What’s the name of the talking snowman in Disney’s Frozen?",
   "Answer": " Olaf"
 },
 {
   "NR": 124,
   "Question": " What do the wheel’s on the bus do in the song?",
   "Answer": " Go round and round"
 },
 {
   "NR": 125,
   "Question": " What is taller, an elephant or a giraffe?",
   "Answer": " A giraffe (they are the tallest animal and can grow up to nearly six metres tall!)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 126,
   "Question": " Who are Harry Potter’s two best friends?",
   "Answer": " Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger"
 },
 {
   "NR": 127,
   "Question": " What’s the name of the cowboy in Toy Story?",
   "Answer": " Woody"
 },
 {
   "NR": 128,
   "Question": " How many planets are in our solar system?",
   "Answer": " Eight"
 },
 {
   "NR": 129,
   "Question": " How many players are in a football team?",
   "Answer": " 11 players"
 },
 {
   "NR": 130,
   "Question": " How many zeros are there in one thousand?",
   "Answer": " Three"
 },
 {
   "NR": 131,
   "Question": " Name all five Brontë sisters",
   "Answer": " Emily, Elizabeth, Charlotte, Anne and Maria"
 },
 {
   "NR": 132,
   "Question": " Which Stephen King novel takes place mostly in the fictional Overlook Hotel?",
   "Answer": " The Shining"
 },
 {
   "NR": 133,
   "Question": " What do Lord of the Rings author J R R   Tolkien’s initials stand for?",
   "Answer": " John Ronald Reuel"
 },
 {
   "NR": 134,
   "Question": " What is the best-selling novel of all time?",
   "Answer": " Don Quixote"
 },
 {
   "NR": 135,
   "Question": " Who authored The Hunger Games book series?",
   "Answer": " Suzanne Collins"
 },
 {
   "NR": 136,
   "Question": " Which planet has the most moons?",
   "Answer": " Saturn"
 },
 {
   "NR": 137,
   "Question": " What part of a plant conducts photosynthesis?",
   "Answer": " Leaf"
 },
 {
   "NR": 138,
   "Question": " How many elements are in the periodic table?",
   "Answer": "118"
 },
 {
   "NR": 139,
   "Question": " Where is the smallest bone in the human body located?",
   "Answer": " Ear"
 },
 {
   "NR": 140,
   "Question": " How many hearts does an octopus have?",
   "Answer": "3"
 },
 {
   "NR": 141,
   "Question": " With over 222 million units sold, what is Apple’s highest-selling iPhone model?",
   "Answer": " iPhone 6/6 Plus"
 },
 {
   "NR": 142,
   "Question": " In which year was the Microsoft XP operating system released?",
   "Answer": "2001"
 },
 {
   "NR": 143,
   "Question": " Elon Musk is the CEO of which global brand",
   "Answer": " Tesla"
 },
 {
   "NR": 144,
   "Question": " Which operating system does a Google Pixel phone use?",
   "Answer": " Android"
 },
 {
   "NR": 145,
   "Question": " In which year was the Nintendo 64 released in Europe?",
   "Answer": "1997"
 },
 {
   "NR": 146,
   "Question": " Who sang 1995 song Mysterious Girl?",
   "Answer": " Peter Andre"
 },
 {
   "NR": 147,
   "Question": " Who is the lead singer of Pulp?",
   "Answer": " Jarvis Cocker"
 },
 {
   "NR": 148,
   "Question": " Name Britney Spears first album released in 1999",
   "Answer": " … Baby One More Time"
 },
 {
   "NR": 149,
   "Question": " Who is the former drummer of Nirvana who fronts the Foo Fighters?",
   "Answer": " Dave Grohl"
 },
 {
   "NR": 150,
   "Question": " Who had a hit with MMMBop in April 1997?",
   "Answer": " Hanson"
 },
 {
   "NR": 151,
   "Question": " What year did Dexys Midnight Runners release Come On Eileen?",
   "Answer": "82"
 },
 {
   "NR": 152,
   "Question": " Which Frankie Goes to Hollywood song was banned by the BBC?",
   "Answer": " Relax"
 },
 {
   "NR": 153,
   "Question": " A 1987 number one hit by The Firm parodied which sci-fi show?",
   "Answer": " Star Trek"
 },
 {
   "NR": 154,
   "Question": " Which 1980s band was the Rev Richard Cole a part of?",
   "Answer": " The Communards"
 },
 {
   "NR": 155,
   "Question": " Which former Beatle had a number one hit with Stevie Wonder in 1982?",
   "Answer": " Paul McCartney"
 },
 {
   "NR": 156,
   "Question": " What was the best selling film soundtrack of the 1970s in the UK?",
   "Answer": " Saturday Night Fever"
 },
 {
   "NR": 157,
   "Question": " Which children’s characters famous for living on Wimbledon Common released several novelty singles in the 70s",
   "Answer": " The Wombles"
 },
 {
   "NR": 158,
   "Question": " What is the first line of Queen’s Bohemian Rhapsody?",
   "Answer": " Is this the real life? Is this just fantasy?"
 },
 {
   "NR": 159,
   "Question": " John Denver’s Take Me Home Country Roads is about which US state?",
   "Answer": " West Virginia"
 },
 {
   "NR": 160,
   "Question": " True or false: Lynyrd Skynyrd got their name from a strict school P E teacher",
   "Answer": " True"
 },
 {
   "NR": 161,
   "Question": " Name the actress who plays the role of Mike Wheeler in Stranger Things",
   "Answer": " Finn Wolfhard"
 },
 {
   "NR": 162,
   "Question": " When was drama Ozark first released on Netflix?",
   "Answer": "2017"
 },
 {
   "NR": 163,
   "Question": " Which US state was Joe Exotic aka  the Tiger King’s G W Zoo Based",
   "Answer": " Oklahoma"
 },
 {
   "NR": 164,
   "Question": " How many actresses played the part of Queen Elizabeth II in The Crown so far (season 1, 2, 3)?",
   "Answer": " Two (Claire Foy, Olivia Coleman)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 165,
   "Question": " Which former Doctor Who star played the role of a villain in Netflix Marvel series Jessica Jones?",
   "Answer": " David Tennant"
 },
 {
   "NR": 166,
   "Question": " Who killed Tony Stark’s parents?",
   "Answer": " The Winter Soldier"
 },
 {
   "NR": 167,
   "Question": " What Top Gun character is Captain America’s cat named after?",
   "Answer": " Goose"
 },
 {
   "NR": 168,
   "Question": " Director Taika Waititi also played which comedic Thor: Ragnarok character?",
   "Answer": " Korg"
 },
 {
   "NR": 169,
   "Question": " Natasha Romanova is the real name of which superhero?",
   "Answer": " Black Widow"
 },
 {
   "NR": 170,
   "Question": " What is the highest-grossing Marvel movie without the word ‘Avengers’ in the title?",
   "Answer": " Black Panther"
 },
 {
   "NR": 171,
   "Question": " Name the eldest Weasley sibling",
   "Answer": " Bill Weasley"
 },
 {
   "NR": 172,
   "Question": " Who does Dobby serve before he is freed by Harry Potter?",
   "Answer": " The Malfoy family"
 },
 {
   "NR": 173,
   "Question": " Who is Fluffy?",
   "Answer": " Three-headed dog"
 },
 {
   "NR": 174,
   "Question": " What is the longest Harry Potter film? (Non-extended versions)",
   "Answer": " Chamber of Secrets (161 minutes)"
 },
 {
   "NR": 175,
   "Question": " What is the effect of the Obliviate spell?",
   "Answer": " Removes memories"
 },
 {
   "NR": 176,
   "Question": " Where was Frida Kahlo born?",
   "Answer": " Mexico"
 },
 {
   "NR": 177,
   "Question": " Café Terrace at Night is an 1888 oil painting by which Dutch master?",
   "Answer": " Vincent Van Gogh"
 },
 {
   "NR": 178,
   "Question": " Where is the original Starry Night by Vincent Van Gogh housed?",
   "Answer": " Museum of Modern Art, New York"
 },
 {
   "NR": 179,
   "Question": " In which century did Rembrandt live?",
   "Answer": " 17th"
 },
 {
   "NR": 180,
   "Question": " In what decade was celebrated artist Tracy Emin born?",
   "Answer": " 1960s"
 },
 {
   "NR": 181,
   "Question": " What is the capital of Bulgaria?",
   "Answer": " Sofia"
 },
 {
   "NR": 182,
   "Question": " What is the capital of New Zealand?",
   "Answer": " Wellington"
 },
 {
   "NR": 183,
   "Question": " Beirut is the capital of which country?",
   "Answer": " Lebanon"
 },
 {
   "NR": 184,
   "Question": " What is the capital of Canada?",
   "Answer": " Ottawa"
 },
 {
   "NR": 185,
   "Question": " Hanoi is the capital of which country?",
   "Answer": " Vietnam"
 },
 {
   "NR": 186,
   "Question": " What is the capital of Argentina?",
   "Answer": " Buenos Aries"
 },
 {
   "NR": 187,
   "Question": " The capital of Iceland is?",
   "Answer": " Reykjavik"
 },
 {
   "NR": 188,
   "Question": " Slovakia’s capital is?",
   "Answer": " Bratislava"
 },
 {
   "NR": 189,
   "Question": " What’s the capital of Belgium?",
   "Answer": " Brussels"
 },
 {
   "NR": 190,
   "Question": " What is the capital of Brazil?",
   "Answer": " Brasilia"
 },
 {
   "NR": 191,
   "Question": " What is the official name of the clock tower commonly referred to as Big Ben?",
   "Answer": " Elizabeth Tower"
 },
 {
   "NR": 192,
   "Question": " In 1952 Albert Einstein was offered the Presidency of which country?",
   "Answer": " Israel"
 },
 {
   "NR": 193,
   "Question": " What colour are the seats in the House of Commons?",
   "Answer": " Green"
 },
 {
   "NR": 194,
   "Question": " What year did Britain join the EEC, now knows as the European Union?",
   "Answer": "1973"
 },
 {
   "NR": 195,
   "Question": " In which state was former US President Barack Obama born?",
   "Answer": " Hawaii"
 },
 {
   "NR": 196,
   "Question": " O’Hare Airport serves which American city?",
   "Answer": " Chicago"
 },
 {
   "NR": 197,
   "Question": " Bohemian Switzerland National Park is in which country?",
   "Answer": " Czech Republic"
 },
 {
   "NR": 198,
   "Question": " Which lake is often described as the jewel of the Italian lakes?",
   "Answer": " Lake Como"
 },
 {
   "NR": 199,
   "Question": " In which country would you find the original Legoland?",
   "Answer": " Denmark"
 },
 {
   "NR": 200,
   "Question": " Which island group includes Ibiza, Menorca and Majorca?",
   "Answer": " The Balearics"
 },
 {
   "NR": 201,
   "Question": " A DNA molecule is described as being what shape?",
   "Answer": " Double helix"
 },
 {
   "NR": 202,
   "Question": " Botany is the study of what life form?",
   "Answer": " Plants"
 },
 {
   "NR": 203,
   "Question": " Which process converts sugar to acids, alcohol or gases?",
   "Answer": " Fermentation"
 },
 {
   "NR": 204,
   "Question": " Which chamber of the heart pumps deoxygenated blood to the lungs?",
   "Answer": " Right ventricle"
 },
 {
   "NR": 205,
   "Question": " What is the largest animal on the planet?",
   "Answer": " Blue whale"
 }
]